Curriculum vitae

Camilo Andrés Morán López

Software Engineer - Full Stack Developer

Phone number: (+57) 3183518130

Email: camiloandresmoran@gmail.com



Summary

Electronic engineer autodidact, self-motivated, hands-on, goal-oriented person with experience in software and hardware development such as .Net6/.Net7, JavaScript/Typescript, NodeJS, Bootstrap, W3.CSS, React and Angular 18. I have experience working with relational databases such as MySQL and SQLServer and non-relational databases such as MongoDB for documental databases, Neo4J for graph databases and Redis for key value databases. Almost all the time I improve my skills as a software developer learning new technologies and applying the best forms for doing code. I have a great analytical capacity and I have a purpose in the search for new ideas in my projects. Also, I used cloud technologies such as AWS and Azure DevOps. For version control I used GitHub and GitLab. And in almost every project I used SCRUM as an agile method.

Technical Knowledge

Frontend: Angular 2+ (Angular Material), React, Bootstrap, CSS, SCSS, HTML,

Javascript/Typescript

Backend: .NET 6/7. NodeJS

Databases: MySQL, SQLServer, MongoDB, Redis

DevOps: Continuous Integration – Pipelines Development YAML

Version Control: GitLab – GitHub – Tfs – Bitbucket.

Agile methodologies: Scrum

Agile project management: Azure DevOps – JIRA – Open Project.

Cloud: Microsoft Azure, AWS.

Web experience: Rest API/Soap, MVC, Layered Architecture, Microservices,

Single Page Applications, JSON/XML, Docker, Kubernetes.

Integrations tools: Apache Nifi

Languages

English B2 Upper-Intermediate

Reading: High

Writing: High

Listening: High

Conversational: High

Education

Pontificia Universidad Javeriana

Degree: Studies in systems and computing engineering - 2023

Pontificia Universidad Javeriana

Degree: Electronic engineering - 2013

Experience

SATRACK

June 2023 at present

ACTIVITIES: Develop engineer. I worked as a full stack developer using Angular 12 in frontend, .NET 7 for backend and SQLServer for database. Also, I am using Docker and Kubernetes for deploying integration tools as Apache Nifi for getting data for external customers. Using Continuous integration with Azure DevOps

BANKOR

January 2023 – June 2023

ACTIVITIES: Develop engineer. I worked as a full stack developer using React and Angular 16 in frontend, ASP.NET for backend and SQLServer for database. Using Continuous integration with Azure DevOps

KATARY SOFTWARE FACTORY

January 2021 - January 2023

ACTIVITIES: Contratacion— Develop engineer. I worked as a full stack developer in medical applications using NodeJS and Angular 18, and in the backend using Microsoft .NET and MongoDB for the database.

KATARY SOFTWARE FACTORY

November 2022 – February 2023

ACTIVITIES: SIGMEP – Develop engineer. I worked as a full stack developer in medical applications using NodeJS and Angular, and in the backend using Microsoft .NET and SQL Server for the databases. This was a migration project.

KATARY SOFTWARE FACTORY

September 2022 – February 2023

ACTIVITIES: Genex Services – Develop engineer. I worked as a full stack developer in medical applications using Java, ETLs working with C# and SQL Server for the databases. Using Continuous integration with Azure DevOps.

KATARY SOFTWARE FACTORY

September 2021 – January 2022

ACTIVITIES: Pichincha Bank – PPM maintenance. I worked on tasks for maintenance on some web platforms such as Laravel 5, NodeJS with React and NodeJS with ReactJS. Most of the activities are related to modifying the appearance of the Grande Table website. That was made in NodeJS and React. For resolving tasks about sending data between interfaces or getting the status in the application I use LocalStorage and Hooks. For sending data to Database I use Axios as a tool that allows you to make requests to a given endpoint.

KATARY SOFTWARE FACTORY

August 2016 - September 2021

ACTIVITIES: Urkunina building Company. I worked in planning building projects, inventory control and software for planning machine maintenance. Technologies used: React native, NodeJS, MySQL.

KATARY SOFTWARE FACTORY

January 2017 – July 2017

ACTIVITIES: SODEXO: SME web application was made for marketing of bonuses and employee benefit cards. Technologies were used: React native and NodeJS for frontend and backend. MySQL for databases.

KATARY SOFTWARE FACTORY

January 2016 – January 2017

ACTIVITIES: SODEXO: BExpert web application to improve the diagnosis, simulation and approval of tax benefits in relation to the salary of employees. Technologies used: React native, NodeJS, MySQL, MongoDB.

TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY OF PEREIRA

Teacher as Web technologies

August 2021 - December 2021

ACTIVITIES: I was a teacher of web technologies such as HTML, CSS, NodeJS, ReactJS, Bootstrap.

CORPORACIÓN AUTÓNOMA DE NARIÑO

Teacher as programming languages

January 2018 – June 2018

ACTIVITIES: I was a teacher of programming languages such as C/C++, MATLAB/Simulink and VHDL for making electronic digital systems.

CONTROLTEC LTDA

Developer in PHD

June 2012 – February 2013

ACTIVITIES: I was a developer for fatigue system in Matlab using Artificial Intelligence systems for detecting breakpoints in materials

JAVERIANA UNIVERSITY

Teacher assistance

February 2012 – June 2012

ACTIVITIES: I was an assistant for teaching programming languages such as C/C++, MATLAB/Simulink, LabVIEW and VHDL.